Yeah, I mean, those guys came and fixed that on the back of that.
Nah, let's try that one.
What do you say?
I went out there and just kind of got to stay tonight.
There's a stream coming out.
It's not as bad as it was before.
What are you doing in the mud?
Oh, that's okay.
Did I get rid of it all the way in that road right there?
Is that what the flag grew up there?
Yeah, they just get all of that.
I ran over all of them.
I have.
They're just messing with you.
They all are.
They're there and you hear, but they're not there.
I'm confused.
They didn't want you.
So don't make it a little different.
Sounds like a solution.
That's a rebound.
Oh, do you hear that?
Stop.
Are the guys in the back?
You guys are ready back there?
They're ready.
Yeah, it's six o'clock.
It's the same thing.
So that's just the same thing.
Normally, we can keep the people out.
We got a guy who's kind of a parent.
Gonna out.
I got a parent.
All right, Ellen, now call to order the special utility authority meeting for a Tuesday, January
23rd.
I'd like to call for a brand-in-fletcher to give our invocation.
I'd probably like to add with love you.
We're thankful for this chance to meet together as community leaders.
I've got a weed-staffs that you would bless this time.
Father, I pray that a love and a passion for this community will unite these leaders and
allow them to make the best decisions for us going forward to be a great community.
Father, again, we love you.
We thank you for Jesus, and we ask that we would be more like him, and to his name we pray.
Amen.
I'd like to lead you to the United States of America and to the Republic for which it stands.
One nation under God, an individual with liberty and justice for all.
All right, number four, public input and unscheduled personal panches.
We have none.
We can sit at agenda.
The board asks so we approve items six and seven.
If I may point out, you were all provided a revised claims list.
And on that, it provides claims list.
a particular item on the second page for lease concrete for $34,416 dollars, that was missed
on the original claim list to be added.
But what that does do is put us in a situation where council movement subverts are
able to say somebody will do a claim that's not going to be a motion to approve.
I'd like a motion.
Sorry.
Okay.
Thank you.
All right.
Number eight.
Budget amendment.
Geofit's given.
This is part two of a two part amendment.
The first one is for the amendment.
Well, this is really the second part of the party.
This is the MSUA accepting 150,15738 from the Capital Improvement Fund and spending it
on purchasing property 124 North Main Street and then on the council meeting, I'll have
the first of that part A.
To note, we have already received the money.
It was on December 30th.
We received the money from the Ottawa County abstract for that property already.
So.
Any questions?
Thank you.
Second.
Marker.
Williams.
Don't go.
All right.
Number nine.
Davis Wright.
Tremaine Claim for Pins College.
RDA Realizes and Associated Complaint Proceeding in the amount of $69,044.
So, council.
If you recall during our last council meeting, I had mentioned that there was at least one
more large outstanding invoice to come from all of the GRDF that it studied report.
This is that invoice that I spoke of.
It is a large invoices was anticipated and in front of you, you should have a revised BA that
has included the totals of the funding that's provided in the budget.
The $750,000 was budget.
We have remaining in that.
$613,000 for 50,000 for 23.
And so this $69,000 would go against that.
So the $69,000 is included in the 1.36.
Or it's.
So the $69,000 would add.
$9.00.
to the 136, but we're still several 100,000 under what we budget.
Any other questions?
Did you make a motion to approve?
Can we get a second?
Hi.
Senator.
Thank.
Part 2.
Okay.
Number 10.
Resolution MSUA-2023-1.
Part 1.
Part 2.
Participation in the municipal electric systems of Oklahoma inks.
Mutual aid agreement and approved mutual aid agreement.
So I was talking about 10 and 11 because they're both very similar.
So this is our mutual aid agreement that we have with MISO and the other ones of the American public
our association.
So any time we would have a big storm that we would require more crews than what we have.
Then we could call on the our mutual aid agreement to have in other cities come help us.
And we've that since I've been here, we've had other cities come help us once.
And we've sent crews.
Every year we use these things crews to different places.
You know, ice storms, tornadoes, different things like that.
And we get reimbursed for it.
And they pay us, you know, on our equipment based on fumarates.
And the employees, they get paid, you know, if they're either time and a half time, whatever, you know, that they're on.
So it is a good deal for all of us, you know, because there is times that we don't have enough crews for everybody.
But we do get reimbursed for everybody.
Yes, sir.
Yeah.
Tyler, what's the difference between the American public power and MISO?
So MISO is just small.
You know, pretty much with Oklahoma cities.
There's maybe one or two Arkansas cities.
And like, like, off-heal Kansas, where APPA is nationwide.
So there's, there's a few Oklahoma cities.
There are APPA, like Clairemore.
You see Clairemore goes a lot over the country to help out.
So there are APPA members.
So, and I think this also helps us because, you know, we may have a huge storm that goes through and takes out Oklahoma.
Or we really couldn't ask for help for Oklahoma crews, but maybe we could ask for, you know, somebody around Kansas City, let's say,
or St. Louis or something like that, you know, through the APPA.
So.
Just have to include anybody in, and like the Southern Southwest Missouri area.
Yes, sir.
Okay.
And this, we've always had this in the past, right?
Yes, sir.
Yeah, this is just, we just, they asked us to update it, so we updated it for the year.
Good. Any other questions?
Do we vote on these separately?
I'm like in motion to approve.
Soon enough.
Uh
I
am.
Yes sir is it this and this is a city of the American
College Power Association.
Um
Armin actually I'm sorry line at him 12
potentially new other business, which has not, which is a resistance
supposing this agenda, that none, trustee, community announcements, and the number
14, the meeting will be continuing for council chambers and reconvened in the
staff room for purposes of the executive session and to completion of agenda
item 14 of the regular meeting of the Madame City Council.